https://www.celebnakedness.com/tour/privacy.php

Members     |     Home     |     A-Z     |     Links     |     Reviews     |     Top 10s     |     Get Access
Suggestions: nude sextape bikini lesbian hidef oops lingerie seethrough cleavage pokies or Search: For Celebs by Occupation, Age...
Effective Date: October 1, 2014
Thank you for visiting this site operated by Sergio, Inc (the "Site"). We are committed to protecting your privacy online and to providing you with the very best experience we can on the Site. In order to do so, we may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
What information do we collect?
When you visit the Site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited, types of products purchased, and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve the Site and make your experience on the Site as valuable and efficient as possible.
When you sign up with us or become a Site member, you may be asked to provide the following personal information to us or one of our third-party processors:
First and last name
Billing address
Email address
Phone number
Credit card account number
What information do other parties collect?
In addition to our credit card processors, some advertisers or websites that have links on the Site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. We do not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
What are cookies and how do we use them?
The Site may use cookies to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored content. We also use cookies to remember information you gave us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. By showing us how and when members and shoppers use the Site, cookies also help us see which areas are popular and which are not. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our sponsors and advertisers. Some advertisers or websites that have links on the Site may also use their own cookies.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. You will not be able to log in, view clips or order from the Site if you turn off the cookies option.
Credit card processing and security
Credit card security is an important aspect of the online experience. In order to keep your credit card information safe, your ordering information -- including your name, address, and credit card number -- is encrypted using a secure server, so that your credit card and billing information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system.
Credit-card transactions are handled by a third-party financial institution or gateway processor, which receives the credit card number and other personal identifying information only to verify the credit card numbers and process transactions. We also offer other payment options via our join page and as a last resort you can pay by certified check and send it by mail to us. Please contact Customer Support for how to proceed using certified checks.
Cooperation with law enforcement
We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use the Site for illegal activities. We reserve the right to release information about members who we believe are in violation of applicable laws or regulations. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful.
Security
The Site's member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. We take precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of our member information at any time.
Users Located Outside of the United States
We make an effort to protect the personal information of all users of the Site. If you are unsure whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the rules applicable where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to the Site. IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION. Users of the Site located in countries outside of the United States who submit personal information do thereby consent to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States.
COPPA compliance
The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We assume products purchased through credit card means are purchased by adults. We have designed this privacy policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.
If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from its active database.
We believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.
California User Consumer Rights.
Under California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: http://www.ftc.gov.
Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information that we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the folloi #wing address: SK Intertainment, Privacy Rights, 1625 North Damen Avenue, Floor 2, Chicago, Illinois 60647.
Business transitions
In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of our assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
Your consent
By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this policy, and you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically.
Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to sbaldis@sympatico.ca.
Members     |     Home     |     A-Z     |     Links     |     Webmasters     |     Contact         Get Access
Billing Support - Privacy - Terms and Conditions - 2257 exempt
© Sergio Inc. all celebs/models are 18 years or older
